Welcome to our training on best practices for getting reviews and ratings in this
training you'll learn how to accurately represent your product on your product
detail page how to provide a great order experience for customers and how to use
feedback manager when a customer buys a product in the Amazon store they can
choose to leave a product review and a seller feedback rating a product review
is a customer's description of a product's quality function and usefulness a
seller feedback rating reflects how a customer feels about a seller's
reliability the quality of a seller's products and the overall fulfillment
experience reviews and ratings are key to the Amazon shopping experience customers
often refer to other customers reviews and ratings to make informed buying
decisions Getting reviews and ratings can take time let's go over three best
practices you can follow to improve your chances of getting reviews and
ratings the first best practice is to accurately present your product on your
product detail page this page includes a product's title images description
variations like size and color and bullet points highlighting key features when
customers place an order in the Amazon store they expect the product to arrive
exactly as it's presented on the product detail page to ensure your product is
accurately represented use multiple high quality images to showcase product
features from different angles provide important product information in your
title description and bullet points and highlight key features customers should
consider such as product dimensions age appropriateness ideal product conditions
and more by accurately representing your product on your product detail page
customers will know exactly what to expect and you'll improve your chances
for getting reviews and ratings a second best practice is to provide a great
order experience for customers to do this consider the following ensure your
product packaging protects your product from damage during transit to the
customer ship all orders on time so they arrive within the time frame you
provide ensure your inventory quantity is correct if it's incorrect your
customers might buy products that are out of stock offer customers full refunds
for products returned within 30 days of purchase acknowledge and reply to all
customer messages within 24 hours provide tracking IDs to help customers
track the delivery of their shipments or send your products to fulfillment by
Amazon or FBA with FBA Amazon stores your inventory ships your orders and
handles returns and customer service finally a third best practice is to
manage and track buyer satisfaction with your service using feedback manager to
access this sign in to seller central hover over performance and select feedback
the recent feedback section of this page lets you view customer feedback comments
and post a public reply customer feedback in this section is ordered by
the date it's received and accompanied by a product's corresponding ID number and
customer rating for more information about feedback manager search for about
feedback manager in seller central this concludes our training on best
practices for getting reviews and ratings you now have the tools to increase your
chances of getting reviews and ratings thank you and happy selling in the
Amazon store